http://www.someonesentyouagreeting.com/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy – Someone Sent You A Greeting
Menu Skip to contentContactAboutCookie PolicyTerms of ServicePrivacy Policy
Search for:
Someone Sent You A GreetingFree eCards, Greetings Card Wishes and Gift Ideas
Menu Skip to contentHomeGreetings Card MessagesAnniversary MessagesBirthday MessagesCongratulations MessagesGraduation MessagesPregnancy CongratulationsWedding MessagesChristmas MessagesLove MessagesEaster MessagesRetirement MessagesHalloween MessagesThank You MessagesMother’s Day MessagesSympathy MessagesNew Years MessagesNew Baby MessagesValentine’s Day MessagesGet Well MessagesQuotationsFather’s Day MessageseCardsBirthday eCardsHappy Birthday eCardsBelated Birthday eCards60th Birthday eCardsBirthday eCards for MomAnniversary eCardsChristmas eCardsSympathy eCardsRetirement eCardsGet Well Soon eCardsNew Baby Congratulations eCardsEngagement Congratulations eCardsPregnancy Congratulations eCardsThank You eCardsThank You Teacher eCardsMother’s Day eCardsHanukkah eCardsGraduation eCardsChristian eCardsThanksgiving eCardsWedding eCardsWedding Congratulations eCardsWedding Thank You eCardsParty Planning & IdeasRetirementResources
Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy:
SomeoneSentYouAGreeting ("SomeoneSentYouAGreeting")
operates someonesentyouagreeting.com and may operate other websites. It
is SomeoneSentYouAGreeting's policy to respect your privacy regarding any information we may collect
while operating our websites.Website VisitorsLike most website operators, SomeoneSentYouAGreeting collects non-personally-identifying information of the
sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference,
referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. SomeoneSentYouAGreeting's purpose in
collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand
how SomeoneSentYouAGreeting's visitors use its website. From time to
time, SomeoneSentYouAGreeting may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g., by
publishing a report on trends in the usage of its website.SomeoneSentYouAGreeting also collects potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol
(IP) addresses for logged in users and for users leaving comments on someonesentyouagreeting.com
blogs/sites. SomeoneSentYouAGreeting only discloses logged in user and commenter IP addresses under the same
circumstances that it uses and discloses personally-identifying information as described below, except that
commenter IP addresses and email addresses are visible and disclosed to the administrators of the blog/site
where the comment was left.Gathering of Personally-Identifying InformationCertain visitors to SomeoneSentYouAGreeting's websites choose to interact
with SomeoneSentYouAGreeting in ways that require SomeoneSentYouAGreeting to gather
personally-identifying information. The amount and type of information that SomeoneSentYouAGreeting gathers
depends on the nature of the interaction. For example, we ask visitors who sign up at someonesentyouagreeting.com to provide a
username and email address. Those who engage in transactions with SomeoneSentYouAGreeting are asked to
provide additional information, including as necessary the personal and financial information required to
process those transactions. In each case, SomeoneSentYouAGreeting collects such information only insofar as
is necessary or appropriate to fulfill the purpose of the visitor's interaction with
SomeoneSentYouAGreeting. SomeoneSentYouAGreeting does not disclose personally-identifying information
other than as described below. And visitors can always refuse to supply personally-identifying information, with
the caveat that it may prevent them from engaging in certain website-related activities.Aggregated StatisticsSomeoneSentYouAGreeting may collect statistics about the behavior of visitors to its
websites. SomeoneSentYouAGreeting may display this information publicly or provide it to others.
However, SomeoneSentYouAGreeting does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as
described below.Protection of Certain Personally-Identifying InformationSomeoneSentYouAGreeting discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information
only to those of its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations that (i) need to know that information
in order to process it on SomeoneSentYouAGreeting's behalf or to provide services available
at SomeoneSentYouAGreeting's websites, and (ii) that have agreed not to disclose it to others. Some
of those employees, contractors and affiliated organizations may be located outside of your home country; by
using SomeoneSentYouAGreeting's websites, you consent to the transfer of such information to
them. SomeoneSentYouAGreeting will not rent or sell potentially personally-identifying and
personally-identifying information to anyone. Other than to its employees, contractors and affiliated
organizations, as described above, SomeoneSentYouAGreeting discloses potentially personally-identifying and
personally-identifying information only in response to a subpoena, court order or other governmental request, or
when SomeoneSentYouAGreeting believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the
property or rights of SomeoneSentYouAGreeting, third parties or the public at large. If you are a registered
user of an SomeoneSentYouAGreeting website and have supplied your email address, SomeoneSentYouAGreeting
may occasionally send you an email to tell you about new features, solicit your feedback, or just keep you up to
date with what's going on with SomeoneSentYouAGreeting and our products. If you send us a request (for
example via email or via one of our feedback mechanisms), we reserve the right to publish it in order to help us
clarify or respond to your request or to help us support other users. SomeoneSentYouAGreeting takes all
measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration or destruction of
potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information.CookiesA cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor's computer, and that the visitor's browser
provides to the website each time the visitor returns. SomeoneSentYouAGreeting uses cookies to
help SomeoneSentYouAGreeting identify and track visitors, their usage of SomeoneSentYouAGreeting
website, and their website access preferences. SomeoneSentYouAGreeting visitors who do not wish to have
cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before
using SomeoneSentYouAGreeting's websites, with the drawback that certain features
of SomeoneSentYouAGreeting's websites may not function properly without the aid of cookies.Business TransfersIf SomeoneSentYouAGreeting, or substantially all of its assets, were acquired, or in the unlikely event
that SomeoneSentYouAGreeting goes out of business or enters bankruptcy, user information would be one of the
assets that is transferred or acquired by a third party. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that
any acquirer of SomeoneSentYouAGreeting may continue to use your personal information as set forth in this
policy.AdsAds appearing on any of our websites may be delivered to users by advertising partners, who may set cookies.
These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to
compile information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among
other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This Privacy
Policy covers the use of cookies by SomeoneSentYouAGreeting and does not cover the use of cookies by any
advertisers.Privacy Policy ChangesAlthough most changes are likely to be minor, SomeoneSentYouAGreeting may change
its Privacy Policy from time to time, and in SomeoneSentYouAGreeting's sole
discretion. SomeoneSentYouAGreeting encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to
its Privacy Policy. If you have a someonesentyouagreeting.com account, you might also
receive an alert informing you of these changes. Your continued use of this site after any change in
this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.
Search Search for:
Recent Posts 77 Beach Puns, Quotes and Sayings Perfect for Instagram 45 Soccer Puns to Laugh about the Beautiful Game 39 Hilarious Football Puns 52 of the Best Farewell Quotes 90+ Baby Shower Cake Sayings and Messages
Card MessagesBirthday MessagesAnniversary MessagesChristmas MessagesCongratulations MessagesEaster MessagesFather’s Day MessagesGet Well MessagesGraduation MessagesHalloween MessagesMother’s Day MessagesLove MessagesNew Baby MessagesNew Years MessagesPregnancy CongratulationsQuotationsReligious MessagesRetirement MessagesSympathy MessagesThanksgiving MessagesThank You MessagesValentine’s Day MessagesWedding Messages DMCAPROTECTEDSomeone Sent You a Greeting is your number one place for all your greeting card needs.
Visit us: someonesentyouagreeting.com Email: contact@someonesentyouagreeting.com
© Someonesentyouagreeting.com TagsAnniversary eCards Anniversary Messages Apology Messages Birthday eCards Birthday Messages Christmas eCards Christmas Messages Congratulations Messages Easter Messages Engagement eCards Farewell Messages Father's Day Messages Get Well Messages Get Well Soon eCards Good Luck Messages Graduation eCards Graduation Messages Greetings Card Messages Halloween Messages Hanukkah eCards Jokes Love Messages Mother's Day eCards Mother's Day Messages New Baby eCards New Baby Messages Pregnancy Congratulations Pregnancy eCards Quotations Religious Religious eCards Religious Messages Retirement Retirement eCards Retirement Messages St Patrick's Day Messages Sympathy eCards Sympathy Messages Thanksgiving eCards Thank You eCards Thank You Messages Uncategorized Valentine's Day Messages Wedding eCards Wedding Messages Search for:
ContactAboutTerms of ServicePrivacy Policy Islemag powered by WordPress This website uses cookies to improve your experience. We'll assume you're ok with this, but you can opt-out if you wish.Accept Reject Read MorePrivacy & Cookies Policy
Close
Necessary
Always Enabled
